Art and Architecture of China Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Painting (Box 7)
  - Ming dynasty, 1368-1644 (Box 17)
    - Known Artists (Box 17)
      - Tung Ch'i-Ch'ang, 1555-1636 (Box 22)
        - Cities (Box 22)
          - Honolulu (Box 22)
          - Kansas City (Box 22)
          - Liaoning (Box 22)
          - Nanking (Box 22)
          - New York [Slide box 128] (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Landscape Album (Box 22)
          - Peking (Box 22)
          - Shanghai (Box 22)
          - Stockholm (Box 22)
          - Taipei (Box 22)
      - Wan Pang-Chih (Box 22)
      - Wang Chao, ac.c. 1500 (Box 22)
      - Wang Ch'ien (Box 22)
      - Wang Chien-Chang, ac. 1630-1650 (Box 22)
      - Wang Ch'ung, 1494-1533 (Box 22)
      - Wang Chung-yu, 1368-1398 (Box 22)
      - Wang E, ac.c. 1488-1521 (Box 22)
      - Wang Fu, 1362-1416 (Box 22)
        - Various Titles [Slide boxes 128-129] (Box 22)
        - Cities [Slide box 129] (Box 22)
          - Cleveland (Box 22)
          - Kansas City (Box 22)
          - Peking (Box 22)
          - Taipei (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Literary Gathering in a Mountain Lodge (Box 22)
            - Scholars in a Pine Pavilion (Box 22)
          - Washington (Box 22)
      - Wang Hao (Box 22)
      - Wang Ku-Hsiang, 1501-1568 (Box 22)
      - Wang Li, ac. mid-14th century (Box 22)
        - Various Titles (Box 22)
        - Cities (Box 22)
          - Peking (Box 22)
          - Shanghai (Box 22)
            - Hua-Shan T'u [Slide boxes 129-130] (Box 22)
      - Wang Meng-Jen [Slide box 130] (Box 22)
      - Wang Shih-Ch'ang (Box 22)
      - Wang To, 1592-1652 (Box 22)
      - Wang Wen, 1497-1576 (Box 22)
      - Wen Cheng, 15th century (Box 22)
      - Wen Cheng-Ming, 1470-1559 (Box 22)
        - Various Titles (Box 22)
        - Cities (Box 22)
          - Cleveland (Box 22)
          - Hong Kong (Box 22)
          - Honolulu (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Seven Junipers of Ch'in-Ch'uan (Box 22)
          - Kansas City (Box 22)
          - Liaoning (Box 22)
            - Yen-chiang Tieh-chang (Box 22)
          - London [Slide box 131] (Box 22)
          - Nanking (Box 22)
          - New York (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Eight Songs of the Hsiao Hsiang Rivers (Box 22)
            - Garden of the Unsuccessful Politician (Box 22)
          - Peking (Box 22)
          - Shanghai (Box 22)
          - Suchow (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Trees by River (Box 22)
          - Taipei (Box 22)
            - Various Titles (Box 22)
            - Bamboo (Box 22)
            - Flowers [Slide box 132] (Box 22)
            - Imitating Chao Po-Ssu's Red Cliff (Box 22)
            - Imitating Wu Chen's Landscape (Box 22)
            - Landscape after Wang Meng (Box 22)
            - Old Trees by a Cold Waterfall (Box 22)
            - Snow on the Mountain Passes (Box 22)
            - Spring in Kiangnan (Box 22)
            - Spring Trees after the Rain (Box 22)
            - A Thousand Cliffs Contend for Splendor (Box 22)
            - A Thousand Cliffs Contend for Splendor (Box 22)
      - Wen Chia, 1501-1583 (Box 22)
        - Various Titles (Box 22)
        - Cities (Box 22)
          - Nanking (Box 22)
          - Taipei (Box 22)
      - Wen Po-Jen, 1502-1575 [Slide box 133] (Box 23)
        - Various Titles (Box 23)
        - Cities (Box 23)
          - Cleveland (Box 23)
            - Various Titles (Box 23)
            - Washing the Feet of the Dusty World (Box 23)
            - Water Village (Box 23)
          - Peking (Box 23)
          - Taipei (Box 23)
            - Various Titles (Box 23)
            - After the Autumn Rain (Box 23)
            - Island of Fang-Hu (Box 23)
            - Ten Views of Suchou (Box 23)
      - Wen Shu, 1595-1634 (Box 23)
      - Wen Shu, 1595-1634 (Box 23)
      - Wu Bin, ca. 1568-1621 (Box 23)
        - Various Titles (Box 23)
        - Cities (Box 23)
          - Cleveland (Box 23)
            - Various Titles (Box 23)
            - Five Hundred Disciples of Buddha (Box 23)
            - Greeting the Spring (Box 23)
          - Honolulu (Box 23)
          - Taipei {slide box 134] (Box 24)
            - Various Titles (Box 24)
            - Record of the Year's Holidays (Box 24)
            - Steep Valleys & Flying Springs (Box 24)
      - Wu Pin, Hu Tsung-Jen and Kao Yang (Box 24)
      - Wu Po-Li, c. 1400 (Box 24)
      - Wu Shih-En, 16th century (Box 24)
      - Wu-tsung, c. 1506-1521 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - London (Box 24)
          - Peking (Box 24)
      - Xia Chang, 1388-1470 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsia Chang
      - Xia Zhi (Box 24)
        filed under Hsia Chih
      - Xiang Shengmo, 1597-1658 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsiang Sheng-Mo
      - Xiang Yuanbian, 1525-1590 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsiang Yuan-Pien
      - Xie Huan, ac.c. 1426-1452 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsieh Huan
      - Xie Jin, ac.c. 1560 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsieh Chin
      - Xie Shichen, 1487-after 1567 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsieh Shih-Ch'en
      - Xu Ben, 1335-1380 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsu Pen
      - Xu Lin, ac.c. 1510-1550 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsu Lin
      - Xu Wei, 1521-1593 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsu Wei
      - Xue Susu (Xue Wu), c. 1464-1538 (Box 24)
        filed under Hsueh Wu
      - Yang Wen-Ts'ung, 1597-1645 (Box 24)
      - Yao Shou, 1423-1495 [Slide box 135] (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Album of Landscape (Box 24)
        - Scroll of Miscellaneous Paintings (Box 24)
        - Coll. King Kwei (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Chicago (Box 24)
          - New York (Box 24)
            - Drinking to the Accompaniment of Letters (Box 24)
            - Landscape (Box 24)
          - Taipei (Box 24)
      - Yao Te-Hou (Box 24)
      - Yeh Ch'eng (Box 24)
      - Yeh Shuang-Shih (Box 24)
      - Yen Tzung (Box 24)
      - Yin Hung, 16th century (Box 24)
      - Yin Shan (Box 24)
      - Yu Ch'iu, ac.c. 1570-1590 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Cities Peking (Box 24)
      - Yuan Shang-T'ung, 1570-1655 [Slide box 136] (Box 23)
      - Yun Hsiang, 1585-1655 (Box 23)
      - Zeng Jing, 1564-1647 (Box 23)
        filed under Tseng Ching
      - Zhan He (Zhan Zhonghe), ac.c. 1500 (Box 23)
        filed under Chan Chung-Ho
      - Zhang Hong, 1577-after 1652 (Box 23)
        filed under Chang Hung
      - Zhang Ling, c. 1470-1520 (Box 23)
        filed under Chang Ling
      - Zhang Lu, c. 1464-1538 (Box 23)
        filed under Chang Lu
      - Zhang Ruitu, 1576-1641 (Box 23)
        filed under Chang Jui-T'u
      - Zhang Yu, 1323-1385 (Box 23)
      - Zhao Zuo, ac.c. 1610-1630 (Box 23)
        filed under Chao Tso
      - Zhou Chen, ac.c. 1472-1535 (Box 23)
        filed under Chou Ch'en
      - Zhou Quan (Box 23)
        filed under Chou Ch'uan
      - Zhou Tianqiu, 1514-1595 (Box 23)
        filed under Chou T'ien-Ch'iu
      - Zhou Wei, ac.c. 1368-1390 (Box 23)
        filed under Chou Wei
      - Zhou Wenjing, ac.c. 1430-1460 (Box 23)
        filed under Chou Wen-Ching
      - Zhou Zhimian, ac.c. 1580-1610 (Box 23)
        filed under Chou Chih-Mien
      - Zhu Duan, ac.c. 1506-1521 (Box 23)
        filed under Chu Tuan
      - Zhu Fei, ac.c. 1368-1398 (Box 23)
        filed under Chu Fei
      - Zhu Zhanji (Emperor Xuanzong), 1399-1435 (Box 23)
        filed under Hsuan Tsung
      - Zhuo Di, ac.c. 1400-1425 (Box 23)
        filed under Cho Ti
  - Ch'ing dynasty, 1644-1912 (Box 23)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 23)
      - Various Titles (Box 23)
    - Known Artists (Box 23)
      - Ai Ch'i-Meng, 1708-1780 (Box 23)
      - Ch'a Chi-Tso, 1601-1677 (Box 23)
      - Ch'a Shih-Piao, 1615-1698 (Box 23)
        - Various Titles (Box 23)
        - Cities (Box 23)
          - Cleveland (Box 23)
          - Kansas City (Box 23)
      - Chang Hsin, c. 1744-after 1817 (Box 23)
      - Chang Hsiung, 1803-1886 (Box 23)
      - Chang Hsueh-Tseng, ac.c. 1630-1650 (Box 23)
      - Chang Keng, 1685-1760 [Slide box 137] (Box 23)
      - Chang Shi-Su (Box 23)
      - Chang Tsung-Ts'an, 1686-1756 (Box 23)
      - Chang Yu, 1734-1803 (Box 23)
      - Chao Chih-Ch'ien, 1829-1884 (Box 23)
      - Ch'en Mei, ac. 1730-1742 (Box 23)
        - Various Titles (Box 23)
        - Ch'ing-Ming Festial on the River (Box 23)
      - Ch'en Shu, 1660-1736 (Box 23)
      - Ch'en Tzu, 1634-1711 (Box 23)
      - Ch'eng Cheng-K'ue (Box 23)
      - Cheng Hsieh, 1693-1765 (Box 23)
        - Cities (Box 23)
          - Various Titles (Box 23)
          - Princeton (Box 23)
      - Cheng Min, 1607-1682 (Box 23)
      - Ch'eng T'ing-Lu, 1797-1857 (Box 23)
      - Chiang Chu (Box 23)
      - Chiang T'ing-Hsi, 1669-1732 (Box 23)
      - Ch'ien Feng, 1740-1798 (Box 23)
      - Ch'ien-Lung (Box 23)
      - Ch'ien Tu, c. 1761-1845 (Box 23)
      - Chin Nung (Box 23)
        - Various Titles (Box 23)
        - Figures, Plants & Animals Album [Slide box 138] (Box 23)
        - Landscapes Album (Box 23)
        - Plum Blossoms Album (Box 23)
      - Chin T'ing-Piao (Box 23)
      - Chu Ch'ang, c. mid 17th century (Box 23)
      - Chu Han-Chih, 17th century (Box 23)
      - Chu Lun-Han, 1680-1760 (Box 23)
      - Chu Ta (Box 23)
        filed under Pa-Ta-Shan-Jen
      - Chuang Chiung-Sheng, 1626-1647 (Box 23)
      - Fa Jo-Chen, 1613-1696 (Box 23)
      - Fan Ch'i, 1616-after 1694 (Box 23)
        - Various Titles (Box 23)
        - Cities (Box 23)
          - Cleveland (Box 23)
          - Liaoning [Slide box 139] (Box 24)
            - Various Titles (Box 24)
            - Landscape (1646) (Box 24)
            - Landscape of the Four Seasons (Box 24)
      - Fang I-Chih, ac. mid 17th century (Box 24)
      - Fang Shih-Shu, 1692-1751 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Cleveland (Box 24)
          - Taipei (Box 24)
      - Fu Mei, 1628-1683 (Box 24)
      - Fu Shan, 1607-1684 (Box 24)
      - Ho I, ac.c. 1700 (Box 24)
      - Hsiao Ch'en, ac.c. 1680-1710 (Box 24)
      - Hsiao Yun-Ts'ung, 1596-1673 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Cleveland (Box 24)
            - Album of Seasonal Landscapes (Box 24)
            - Pure Tones Among Hills and Streams (Box 24)
          - Pure Tones Among Hills and Streams (Box 24)
      - Hsieh Sui [Slide box 140] (Box 24)
      - Hsieh Sun, ac.c. 1679 (Box 24)
      - Hsu-Ku, 1825-1896 (Box 24)
      - Hsu Yang, ac.c. 1751-1776 (Box 24)
      - Hu Ch'ing-T'si (Box 24)
      - Hu T'ieh-Mei, 1848-1899 (Box 24)
      - Hu Yu-K'un (Box 24)
      - Hua Yen, 1682-c.1761 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Flowers & Birds Album (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Washington (Box 24)
            - Album of Sixteen Landscape Paintings (Box 24)
      - Huang Hsiang-Chien, 1609-1673 (Box 24)
        - Scenes of Travel (Box 24)
      - Huang Shen, 1687-after 1768 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Four Landscapes & Four Figures [Slide box 141] (Box 24)
        - Reminiscences Album (Box 24)
      - Huang Ting, 1660-1730 (Box 24)
      - Hung Jen, 1610-1663 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Honolulu (Box 24)
            - Various Titles (Box 24)
            - The Coming of Autumn (Box 24)
          - Kansas City (Box 24)
          - Peking (Box 24)
          - Shanghai (Box 24)
      - I Fu-Chiu, 1698-after 1747 (Box 24)
      - Jen Hsiung, 1820-1864 (Box 24)
      - Jen Hsun, 1835-1893 (Box 24)
      - Jen I, 1840-1896 (Box 24)
      - Jen Po-Nien [Slide box 142] (Box 24)
        filed under Jen I
      - Kao Ch'i-P'ei, 1672-1734 (Box 24)
      - Kao Feng-Han, 1683-1748 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Album of Landscapes (Box 24)
        - Album of Paintings (Box 24)
        - Album (Chien-Lu Coll.) (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Cleveland (Box 24)
          - Hong Kong (Box 24)
          - Osaka (Box 24)
      - Kao Hsiang (Box 24)
      - Kao Ts'en, ac.c. 1670 (Box 24)
      - Ku Chien-Lung, 1606-after 1686 (Box 24)
      - K'un Ts'an (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Cities [Slide box 143] (Box 24)
          - Hong Kong (Box 24)
            - Landscape (1660) (Box 24)
          - Peking (Box 24)
          - San Francisco (Box 24)
          - Suchow (Box 24)
          - Taipei (Box 24)
            - Various Title (Box 24)
            - The Dense Grove (Box 24)
      - Kung Hsien, c. 1620-1689 (Box 24)
        - Various Titles (Box 24)
        - Landscapes (Box 24)
        - Landscape Studies (Box 24)
        - Cities (Box 24)
          - Cleveland (Box 24)
          - Hong Kong (Box 24)
          - Honolulu (Box 24)
          - Kansas City (Box 24)
            - Cloudy Peaks (1674) (Box 24)
            - Album of Landscapes (1671) [Slide box 144] (Box 24)
            - River Landscape (Box 24)
          - New York (Box 24)
          - Peking (Box 24)
          - Princeton [Slide box 145] (Box 25)
          - Zurich (Box 25)
      - Lan Shen (Box 25)
      - Lang Shih-Ning, 1688-1768 (Box 25)
        - Various Titles (Box 25)
        - Cities (Box 25)
          - Taipei (Box 25)
            - Various Titles (Box 25)
            - Hundred Horses (Box 25)
            - Landscape (Box 25)
      - Leng Mei, ac. 18th century (Box 25)
      - Li Fang-Ying, 1695-1754 (Box 25)
      - Li Jui-Ch'i, c. 1870- (Box 25)
        for Li Jui-ch'I's copies of Shih T'ao's Flowers and Figures Album, see Shih T'ao
      - Li Shan, c. 1686-1762 (Box 25)
      - Li Shih-Cho, c. 1690-1770 [Slide box 146] (Box 25)
        - Various Titles (Box 25)
        - Cities (Box 25)
          - Kansas City (Box 25)
      - Li Zhaoheng, c. 1592-1662 (Box 25)
      - Liu Yu, ac.c. 1700 (Box 25)
        - Various Titles (Box 25)
        - Landscape (Box 25)
        - Landscapes Inspired by T'ang Poems (Box 25)
      - Lo P'ing, 1733-1799 (Box 25)
        - Various Titles (Box 25)
        - Cities (Box 25)
          - Cleveland (Box 25)
          - Hong Kong (Box 25)
            - Ghosts (Box 25)
          - Princeton [Slide boxes 146-147] (Box 25)
          - Suchow [Slide box 147] (Box 25)
          - Washington (Box 25)
      - Lu Wei, ac.c. 1700 (Box 25)
      - Mei Ch'ing, 1623-1697 (Box 25)
        - Various Titles (Box 25)
        - Cities (Box 25)
          - Cleveland (Box 25)
          - Honolulu (Box 25)
          - Shanghai (Box 25)
      - Mei Keng, 17th century (Box 25)
      - Min Chen, 1730-after 1788 (Box 25)
      - Pa-Ta-Shan-Jen, 1626-1705 (Box 25)
        - Various Titles (Box 25)
        - Albums (Box 25)
        - Handscrolls [Slide box 148] (Box 25)
        - Hanging Scrolls (Box 25)
        - Known Collections (Box 25)
        - Cities (Box 25)
          - Various Titles (Box 25)
          - Cambridge (Box 25)
          - Cleveland (Box 25)
          - Hangchou (Box 25)
          - Honolulu (Box 25)
            - Various Titles (Box 25)
            - Eight Landscapes [Slide box 149] (Box 25)
          - Kansas City (Box 25)
          - Kyoto (Box 25)
          - Melbourne (Box 25)
          - New York (Box 25)
          - Oiso (Box 25)
          - Osaka (Box 25)
          - Peking (Box 25)
          - Princeton [Slide box 150] (Box 25)
            - Various Titles (Box 25)
            - Princeton Album 11-leaf, ca. 1683 (Box 25)
            - Princeton Album 8-leaf, ca. 1692 (Box 25)
          - Shanghai (Box 25)
            - Various Titles (Box 25)
            - Handscrolls (Box 25)
            - Hanging Scrolls (Box 25)
            - Landscapes (Box 25)
            - Album, 1694 (Box 25)
          - Stockholm (Box 25)
          - Suchow (Box 25)
          - Taipei (Box 25)
            - Various Titles (Box 25)
            - Paintings from Life (Box 25)
          - Washington (Box 25)
          - Zurich (Box 25)
      - P'an Kung-Shou, 1741-1794 [Slide box 151] (Box 26)
      - Pien Shou-min, 1684-1752 (Box 26)
      - Shen Cho, ac.c. 1836-1841 (Box 26)
      - Shen Ch'uan, 1682-c.1780 (Box 26)
      - Shen Nan-p'ing, 1725-1780 (Box 26)
        - Various Titles (Box 26)
        - Cities (Box 26)
          - Kobe (Box 26)
          - Nagasaki (Box 26)
          - Tokyo (Box 26)
      - Shih T'ao, ac. 1660-1710 (Box 26)
        - Various Titles (Box 26)
        - Cities [Slide box 152] (Box 26)
          - Boston (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Album of Twelve Landscape Paintings, 1703 (Box 26)
          - Cleveland (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Album of Reminiscences of Ch'in-huai River (Box 26)
          - Hong Kong (Box 26)
            - Illustration of Poems by Su Shih (Box 26)
            - Illustration of Poems by Huang Yen-Ssu (Box 26)
            - O-Mei Mountain (Box 26)
            - Yellow Mountain (Box 26)
          - London (Box 26)
          - Los Angeles (Box 26)
          - Nanking (Box 26)
          - New York [Slide box 153] (Box 26)
            - 16 Lohans (Box 26)
            - Chang-kung's Grotto (Box 26)
            - 36 Peaks of Mt. Huang (Box 26)
            - Bamboo, Wind & Rain (Box 26)
            - Hibiscus, Lotus and Rock (Box 26)
            - Landscape: 9th Festival (Box 26)
            - Returning Home album (Box 26)
            - Wilderness Colors (Box 26)
          - Oiso (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Eight Views of Huang-Shan (Box 26)
          - Osaka [Slide box 154] (Box 26)
          - Peking (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Album of Landscapes after T'ang Poems (Box 26)
            - Four Album Leaves (Box 26)
          - Princeton (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Flowers & Figures Album (Box 26)
          - Shanghai (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Landscape, 1687 (Box 26)
          - Stockholm (Box 26)
            - Album at Wang-Lü T'ang (Box 26)
          - Suchow (Box 26)
          - Taipei (Box 26)
          - Washington (Box 26)
            - Peach Blossom Spring (Box 26)
      - Su Jen-Shan, ac. 19th century [Slide box 155] (Box 26)
      - Sun Ku (Box 26)
      - Tai Hsi, 1801-1860 (Box 26)
        - Cities (Box 26)
          - Cleveland (Box 26)
          - Honolulu (Box 26)
      - Tai Pen-Hsiao, 1621-1691 (Box 26)
      - Tan Ch'ung-Kuang, 1623-1692 (Box 26)
      - Tao Chi (Box 26)
        Filed under Shih T'ao
      - T'an Sung, ac. 18th century (Box 26)
      - T'ang Tai, 1673-after 1751 (Box 26)
      - T'eng Cho, 19th century (Box 26)
      - Ting Kuan-P'eng, ac.c. 1745-1765 (Box 26)
      - Ts'ai Chia, ac.c. 1680-1760 (Box 26)
      - Tsou Che, 1636-c.1708 (Box 26)
      - Tsou I-Kuai, 1686-1772 (Box 26)
      - Tung Pang-ta, 1699-1769 (Box 26)
      - Wang Ch'en, 1720-1797 (Box 26)
      - Wang Chien, 1598-1677 (Box 26)
        - Various Titles (Box 26)
        - Cities (Box 26)
          - Cleveland (Box 26)
          - Taipei (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Imitating Old Masters [Slide box 156] (Box 26)
      - Wang Chih-Ch'eng (Box 26)
      - Wang Hui, 1632-1717 (Box 26)
        - Various Titles (Box 26)
        - Album of 24 Paintings (Box 26)
        - Landscape in 6 Parts (Box 26)
        - Cities (Box 26)
          - Cleveland (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Portrait of An Ch'i (Box 26)
          - Honolulu (Box 26)
            - Various Titles (Box 26)
            - Fishing Village on a Clear Day of Fall (Box 26)
            - Lanscape in the Manner of Chü-Jen (Box 26)
            - Countless Peaks and Vales (Box 26)
          - Washington [Slide box 157] (Box 27)
      - Wang Kai, ac.c. 1677-1705 (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - Cities (Box 27)
          - Cleveland (Box 27)
      - Wang Ping, ac.c. 1736-1795 (Box 27)
      - Wang Shih-Min, 1582-1680 (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - Cities (Box 27)
          - Cleveland (Box 27)
          - Taipei (Box 27)
            - Various Titles (Box 27)
            - Album after Sung & Yüan Masters (Box 27)
          - Washington (Box 27)
      - Wang Shih-Min & Others (Box 27)
      - Wang Shih-Shen (Box 27)
      - Wang Shu-Ku, 1647-c. 1730 (Box 27)
      - Wang Su, 1794-1877 [Slide box 158] (Box 27)
      - Wang Wu, 1632-1690 (Box 27)
      - Wang Yüan-Ch'I, 1642-1715 (Box 27)
        - Cities (Box 27)
          - Various Titles (Box 27)
          - Cleveland (Box 27)
          - New York (Box 27)
          - Taipei (Box 27)
            - Various Titles (Box 27)
            - Landscapes (Box 27)
      - Wang Yun, 1652-c. 1735 (Box 27)
      - Wu Hung, ac.c. 1670-1680 (Box 27)
      - Wu Li, 1632-1718 (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - Cities (Box 27)
          - Peking (Box 27)
          - Taipei [Slide box 159] (Box 27)
            - Landscapes after Sung & Yüan Masters (Box 27)
            - White Clouds, Green Mountains (Box 27)
      - Yang Chin, 1644-1726 (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - Album of Flowers and Fruit (Box 27)
      - Yao Sung, ac.c. 1700 (Box 27)
      - Yao Wen-Han (Box 27)
      - Yeh Hsin, ac.c. 1670 (Box 27)
      - Yen Chung, ac. 19th century (Box 27)
      - Yu Chih-Ting, 1647-1705 (Box 27)
      - Yuan Chiang, ac.c. 1690-1725 (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - Cities (Box 27)
          - Kansas City (Box 27)
      - Yuan Yao, ac. 1720-1780 (Box 27)
      - Yün Hsiang (Box 27)
      - Yun Shou-P'ing, 1633-1690 [Slide box 160] (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - 8-Leaf Album, 1683 (Box 27)
        - Cities (Box 27)
          - Honolulu (Box 27)
            - Various Titles (Box 27)
            - Flower Paintings (Box 27)
          - New York (Box 27)
          - Taipei (Box 27)
            - Various Titles (Box 27)
            - Landscape, hanging scroll (Box 27)
            - Sketches, album (Box 27)
      - Yun Shou-P'ing & Wang Hui (Box 27)
        - Various Titles (Box 27)
        - Flowers & Landscapes (Box 27)
- Republic of China/People's Republic (Box 27)
  [Slide box 161]
  - Artists: B (Box 27)
    - Bai Xueshi (Box 27)
  - Artists: C (Box 27)
    - Various Titles (Box 27)
    - Chang Dai-Chien, 1899- (Box 27)
    - Ch'en Ch'i-K'uan, 1921- (Box 27)
    - Chen Danqing, 1953- (Box 27)
    - Chen Yifei, 1946- (Box 27)
    - Cheng Shifa, 1921- (Box 27)
    - Cui Zifan, 1915- (Box 27)
  - Artists: D (Box 27)
    - Various Titles (Box 27)
    - Dong Shouping (Box 27)
    - Deng Fen, 1892-1963 [Slide box 162] (Box 27)
  - Artists: F (Box 27)
    - Various Titles (Box 27)
    - Fang Zhaoling, 1914- (Box 27)
    - Feng Zikai, 1893-1975 (Box 27)
    - Fu Baoshi, 1904-1965 (Box 27)
    - Fu Shen, 1937- (Box 27)
  - Artists: G (Box 27)
    - Various Titles (Box 27)
    - Gao Xiao-Hua (Box 27)
    - Guan Liang, 1900- (Box 27)
    - Guan Shanyueh, 1912- (Box 27)
  - Artists: H (Box 27)
    - Various Titles (Box 27)
    - Ho Huaishuo, 1941- (Box 27)
    - Hu P'ei-Heng & Others (Box 27)
    - Huang Binhong, 1864-1955 (Box 27)
    - Huang Yongyu, 1924- (Box 27)
    - Huang Zhi, 1864-1955 (Box 27)
    - Huang Zhou, 1925- (Box 27)
  - Artists: J [Slide box 163] (Box 28)
    - Jiang Zhaohe (Box 28)
  - Artists: L (Box 28)
    - Various Titles (Box 28)
    - Li Huasheng, 1944- (Box 28)
    - Li Keran, 1907- (Box 28)
    - Li Kuchan, 1898-1983 (Box 28)
    - Li Ning (Box 28)
    - Li Shan (Box 28)
    - Li Shiqing (Box 28)
    - Li Xiongcai, 1910- (Box 28)
    - Lin Fengmian, 1900- (Box 28)
    - Liu Guosong, 1932- [Slide box 164] (Box 28)
    - Liu Haisu, 1896- (Box 28)
    - Liu Jiyu (Box 28)
    - Liu Lun, 1913- (Box 28)
    - Liu Wei, 1965- (Box 28)